THE THIRD ROCK.
THE BLUE MARBLE.
EARTH.
HOME.
EVERY PERSON, PLACE OR THING WE KNOW … EVERYTHING
WE DO.
EVERY MEMORY WE MAKE.
IT’S HERE.
ON THIS PALE BLUE DOT.
IT’S JUST ONE ROCKY PLANET IN ONE SOLAR
SYSTEM IN ONE GALAXY AMONG BILLIONS.
EVEN AS WE EXPLORE SPACE, WE STUDY OUR HOME
PLANET.
WE SEE IT LIKE NO ONE ELSE.
AN EXPANSIVE ECOSYSTEM-- THE VEGETATION, THE
AIR, THE WATER, THE ICE.
OUR DATA IMPROVES THE WAY WE GROW FOOD AND
HOW WE MANAGE THE LAND WE CULTIVATE.
NASA HAS OVER 20 SATELLITES MEASURING THE
HEIGHT OF OCEANS AND INLAND WATERS, CLOUDS
AND PRECIPITATION, CARBON DIOXIDE AND MUCH
MORE.
FOR DECADES, OUR DATA HAS TRACKED HOW ALL
THESE EARTH SYSTEMS INTERACT.
FROM ABOVE, WE SEE THE CONNECTIONS.
CITIES TRANSITION INTO FARM LANDS.
TRIBUTARIES FLOW INTO RIVERS INTO the Sea.
WINDS MOVE CLOUDS AROUND THE PLANET.
BEYOND THESE OBSERVATIONS, NASA’S ABILITY
TO MODEL AND ANTICIPATE HOW THE PLANET IS
CHANGING HELPS COMMUNITIES AROUND THE WORLD
PREPARE.
WE SEE OUR CHANGING PLANET – HURRICANES,
VOLCANOS, FIRES…
AND WE SEE THE IMPACTS OF HUMANS --- MELTING
ICE, RISING TEMPERATURES.
EARTH’S CLIMATE HAS CHANGED AND IS STILL
CHANGING.
OUR DATA GIVES US THE UNDERSTANDING TO ADAPT
--  AND TO PROTECT OUR HOME PLANET IN NEW
WAYS.
OUR ELECTRIC FLIGHT TECHNOLOGIES WILL REDUCE
FUEL AND SAVE ENERGY.
WE WILL MAKE CLEANER AIR TRAVEL POSSIBLE.
BY UNDERSTANDING OUR CHANGING WORLD, WE IMPROVE
LIVES AND SAFEGUARD OUR FUTURE.
THE FUTURE OF OUR LITTLE ROCK IN THE UNIVERSE.
OUR EARTH.
OUR HOME.